<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>http://mossyconway.github.io/ConwayClohessy/</id><title>The Conway &amp; Clohessy Tree</title><updated>2020-08-28T13:43:40.395477+00:00</updated><author><name>Tomás "Mossy" Conway</name><email>nosepam-family@yahoo.co.uk</email></author><link href="http://mossyconway.github.io/ConwayClohessy/feed.atom" rel="self"/><category term="Genealogy"/><generator uri="http://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.6.1">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>A family tree of the ancestors and relatives of Thomas Conway [b1900 - d1980] and Bridie Clohessy [b1904 - d1986]</subtitle><entry><id>tag:mossyconway.github.io/ConwayClohessy/4</id><title>A Hannan memoir</title><updated>2020-08-28T10:20:00+01:00</updated><content>I received a copy of a memoir written by Thomas Hannan [1874 - 1964], thanks to Hugh Sweeney. Thomas was first-cousin-once-removed to Thomas Conway [1900 - 1980] and his sister Annie was married to Thomas Cusack [1863 - 1925] who was an uncle of Bridie Clohessy [1904 - 1986]. The memoir details Thomas's life growing up in Limerick and Dublin, and he names many of his relatives and where they lived. I have used this information in combination with baptism and land records to find the parents of Bridget Hannan [1830 - 1903] and her aunts, uncles and other relatives. The memoir can be found in the Download section.</content><published>2020-08-28T10:20:00+01:00</published></entry><entry><id>tag:mossyconway.github.io/ConwayClohessy/3</id><title>Added Noonan, Foley and Fitzgerald families</title><updated>2018-03-15T11:02:00+00:00</updated><content>Originally I left out part of the tree because I had found a discrepancy between the information I had received on the Cusacks and the records (avilable online) for some of those people. I chose to leave that part of the tree out until I had a better understanding, because it wasn't clear where the diffeences were coming from. I can now add the relevant people to the tree. Thanks to Jerry Russell and Hugh Sweeney for the information.</content><published>2018-03-15T11:02:00+00:00</published></entry><entry><id>tag:mossyconway.github.io/ConwayClohessy/2</id><title>New Year, New People</title><updated>2018-01-01T12:37:00+00:00</updated><content>Added James Sullivan, Clothilde Cusack, Agnes Gleeson, Bridie Gleeson, Eily Gleeson, Kathleen Geary, Bridget Ryan, May Ryan, Burdis Redford, Luke Hartigan,</content><published>2018-01-01T12:37:00+00:00</published></entry><entry><id>tag:mossyconway.github.io/ConwayClohessy/1</id><title>Move Along Please, Nothing To See Here (Yet!)</title><updated>2017-12-22T12:00:00+00:00</updated><content>The web site has only just been published, so no updates yet, give it some time.</content><published>2017-12-22T12:00:00+00:00</published></entry></feed>